### **Personal Info**

Phone: 9840042253

E-mail:

santosh.neupane.0330@gmail.com

website:

santosh-neupane.com.np

LinkedIn:

linkedin.com/santosh-neupane-0330

Github:

github.com/San0330

### **Hobbies**

Cloud Technology

Full Stack Development

Reading Books

Gardening

# **Achievements**

Achieved top 5% in LinkedIn skill assessment for JavaScript, PHP and CSS

Participated in ICPC Regional Programming Competition, Dhaka,Bangladesh

Participated in various hackathons

# **Hobby Projects**

Advanced Programming in UNIX

 Learning About Linux from "Advanced Programming in UNIX Environment" Book.

#### **UI** Designs

 Implementing some great UIs found from design sites like dribble

### Algorithms

# Santosh Neupane

# Software Engineer

With over 2 years of experience in IT industry, I am dedicated to creating innovative and high-performing solutions. My greatest strength is my problem solving skills, work ethics and ability to implement various software development methodologies.

### **EXPERIENCE**

# Momayo Technology

2022 - Present

Full-stack Developer

- Developed EMIS application with various modules for both university staffs and students.
- Collaborated with clients to define software requirements.
- Participated in architecture, design and implementation of backend features using Laravel, Jquery etc.
- Improved response time of application using SQL optimization technique, caching etc when generating summary reports.

### **Neutroline Pvt Ltd**

2021 - 2022

Software Engineer Intern

- Contributed to Employee Management System.
- Integrated third-party tools and components into application.
- Refactored and improved legacy code.
- Provided guidance to new interns.
- Collaborated with management and development partners regarding software application design status and project progress

### **Skills**

PHP/Laravel ReactJS My SQL

NodeJS Git/Github Tailwind CSS

Flutter Docker

### **EDUCATION**

Master in IT 2023 - Present

Tribhuvan University, Kathmandu

### Bachelor in CSIT

2016 - 2021

Nepathya College, Butwal